<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Projects on Clément Allavena</title><link>/projects/</link><description>Recent content in Projects on Clément Allavena</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>fr</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>HAL</title><link>/projects/hal/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/projects/hal/</guid><description>Link Github
Summary Project of IT Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s Degree.
HAL is a Hyper Monitoring project meant for retrieve some data in an IT park and send them into a server managed by the SysAdmin, in goal to agregate the data and handle them. To do so, HAL use a plugin system, which are loaded automaticaly at the start of the client.
Severals languages are available for writing the plugins:
C/C++/C#/Go (.</description></item><item><title>AKHQ</title><link>/projects/akhq/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/projects/akhq/</guid><description>Link Github upstream repo Github forked repo AKHQ official website
Summary AKHQ is an open-source project that is a Kafka GUI for Apache Kafka to manage topics, topics data, consumers group, schema registry, connect and more&amp;hellip;
It was originaly created by tchiotludo but i&amp;rsquo;m a contributor of the open-source project.
Feel free to discover this project with the link above !</description></item><item><title>PromZ</title><link>/projects/promz/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/projects/promz/</guid><description>Link Github
Summary This is a project i&amp;rsquo;ve made during my first internship during my two years University Diploma in Computer Science (DUT in France) at the DOSI of the UCA.
The aim of this project was to provide a end-to-end solution of a full working version of Prometheus and it&amp;rsquo;s exporters, with the Grafana solution to monitoring the data retrieve.
So this repository brings a solution to that problem, only using bash scripting and Perl, and also bring a genericity of the version you want to install.</description></item><item><title>CoFiAppV1</title><link>/projects/cofiappv1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 00:02:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>/projects/cofiappv1/</guid><description>Link Github
Summary This project was the first big project realise during my DUT in Computer Science at UCA (Two years university diploma in France)
It&amp;rsquo;s a database of Movies and series, the difference between other DB is that this one is fill only by user, made it a Community DB.
Made in C#, the UI is orriented Master-Details style.
README of the projects The Readme of the project (only in French):</description></item></channel></rss>